Email: equilinquin@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/elizabeth-garcia-quilinquin-207834191

GitHub: https://github.com/equilinguin Portfolio: https://cryptic-refuge-76006.herokuapp.com/

Elizabeth Garcia-Quilinquin

Full Stack Developer with experience in astronomy outreach to better build a web experience for the public in technology. Recently earned a certificate in Full Stack Developer at the University of Oregon, and prior knowledge of coding with the University of Hawaii Astronomy program. Known as a fast learner, able to pick up new skills and knowledge in an ever-fast-growing field like technology. Great attention to detail that helps with debugging code very quickly and precisely when combing through files. Open to feedback by team members and supervisors when working on projects and able to communicate issues. Worked individually and in a group, to solve issues: debugging code and pinpoint errors in project works and to help others debug project code and constant communication with project work. With this experience as a developer, I someday want to create new apps or computer applications that make a UI experience better education tools on the web.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Javascript

jQuery

• ES6

Web API

NodeJS

React JS

PWA

MERN Stack

MySQL

MongoDB

PROJECTS

Burger App — https://stark-gorge-80987.herokuapp.com/

GitHub-https://github.com/equilinguin/Burger

This app connects to a database and gives a user access to add to the database on an HTML page.

• HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Font Awesome, MySQL, Bootstrap, Heroku

Weather Forecast — https://equilinguin.github.io/Weather-Forecast/

GitHub-https://github.com/equilinguin/Weather-Forecast

This app connects to an API that renders weather data for a city selected.

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, API

StarGazer — https://limitless-atoll-63723.herokuapp.com/

GitHub-https://github.com/alpinelife37/Project-2

This app creates and logs users in, and to make searches of 88 constellations. Future development will ensure individual user experience.

• HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, jQuery, Node, NPM, MySql, Heroku

EXPERIENCE

Whole Foods Market, Hillsboro — Supervisor

May 2017 - PRESENT

- Oversee operations of the department and supervise Team Members in their tasks.
- Cook and prep for different food items that are displayed in our deli, hotbar, and prepack stations.
- Write production lists for scheduled cooks in the kitchen and communicating tasks need to be done to finish lists.
- Training and providing feedback for Team Members for better productivity.
- Understanding and communicating Team Member concerns with Management.

Oregon Museum of Science and Industry (OMSI), Portland — Space Science Educator

August 2017 - October 2019

- Present scheduled shows, and educated guests on accurate information of astronomy.
- Organized and present full length star shows in a timely manner (25 min).
- Communicated errors with live or scheduled shows to the Manager.
- Provided feedback to encourage new shows for the planetarium.

Roxy's Island Grill, Beaverton — *Manager*

March 2014 - May 2017

- Trained new employees on restaurant process and safety procedures.
- Ran and operated FOH and BOH tasks when help is needed.
- Filled venue orders for all restaurants and communicated to use overstock from one to another.
- Communicated with FOH and BOH of OOS (Out of Stock) items, schedule changes, duties, etc.

EDUCATION

University of Oregon, Portland, OR — *Full Stack Web Development Certificate*October 2019 - April 2020

University of Hawaii, Hilo, HI — *Bachelor's Degree in Science - Astronomy* August 2007 - December 2011